why is that?

my code now is:

wgz=0;

writel(wgz,addr+ADCTSC);
tmp=readl(addr+ADCTSC);
printk(tmp);

//but the result is still the former value of ADCTSC not 0

why? why i can not write ADCTSC, while i write ADCCON successfully!

//i repeat, i didnot mistake the adress, cause the value i get 0x58

is the right initial value of ADCTSC.

ANSWER:

haha, the bug is gone when clk_get() is used in my driver
